gotmortgage.com 2009-04-18

# Welcome to Gotmortgage.com Wholesale Lending

Overview

You take your privacy seriously and so does gotmortgage.com We are a company committed to protecting the personal information and privacy of our customers. This statement is one way of sustaining your trust in our company, our products and our services.

Privacy (Website Visitors)

Our Online Privacy Statement describes how we collect, protect and use information about you either during your visit to our web site or when you are a gotmortgage.com customer.

Information We Collect About You during Your Online Visit

Website Visitors / Registered Users

When you browse our site as a visitor or are a registered user of this website, we may collect and store information about your online visit (see cookies). This information may include the time and length of your visit, the pages you view on our site, the last site you visited before coming to ours, and the name of your internet service provider.

We use this data on an aggregate basis to measure site activity, and on an individual basis to make the site more useful and provide information that may be of interest to you.

Registered Users Only

Information collected about registered users is used and shared in accordance with our customer privacy notice and practices. If you are an existing customer, please see the Information Collection and Sharing Practices for Existing Customer section for more information.

As a registered user, you may use the website to:

•           Provide information to us about you when you complete an online application or other form 

•           Provide information to us about you during web page registration 

•           Provide information to us about you during personal profile updates 

Security Statement

About our Website(s)

Cookies

We may use Web cookies for security purposes to recognize your computer when you log into your account. We may also make use of Web cookies or similar data on certain parts of our Web site for fraud prevention and other purposes. If you disable your Web browser's ability to accept our Web cookies, it may not be possible for you to access your online account.

Passwords

Your access to certain portions of our Web site may be protected with an individualized username and password. Your username and password are confidential and personal to you, and should never be disclosed or shared with anyone else.

Timed logout

Certain portions of our Web site may be protected with a timed-logout feature. This can help protect your account from being viewed or used by others if your computer becomes unattended.

Encryption

We may use encryption to protect your information as it travels across the Internet. This can help prevent others from eavesdropping on your browser sessions with our Web servers.

Firewalls

Our Web site may be protected with firewall technology, which can help prevent your account information and our Web site from being improperly accessed.

Surveillance

Certain portions of our Web site are monitored by advanced surveillance and logging technologies. These technologies can help to ensure that both your information and our Web servers are protected from compromise.

Information Collection and Sharing Practices for Existing Customers

Existing Customer/Registered Users

If you are a gotmortgage.com customer details about the information we collect and how it may be disclosed is contained in our Privacy Notice, which includes additional information regarding your privacy choices. Briefly, we collect information about you for example, when you:

•           Apply for a loan 

•           Make your monthly payment 

We also collect personal information from you or others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, employers, or others

Information We Share About Our Existing Customers

The information contained in this section applies to gotmortgage.com customers

We may collect and subsequently share personal information about you to:

•           Run our everyday business 

•           Respond quickly to customer needs 

•           Help us communicate with you 

•           Evaluate eligibility for additional products and services that may be of interest to you 

What We Share

We may share personal information that includes, but is not limited to your:

•           Name, address, and other account application information 

•           Account balances, transactions, and payment history 

•           Creditworthiness including credit history and credit score 

With Whom We Share

We disclose some of the information we collect about you to third parties such as credit reporting agencies, regulators and loan investors. These types of third parties are called non-affiliated third parties.

We may also share some of this information with companies performing services on our behalf such as the vendor who prepares and mails our monthly statements. These types of vendors are called service providers.

We may share information we collect about you with companies with whom we have formal agreements to offer you financial products and services. These types of relationships are called joint marketing partnerships.

Finally, we may share information we collect about you with companies related by common control  to offer you products and services that may be of interest to you. These types of companies are called affiliates.

Benefits of sharing

We need to collect and share information about our customers to help us communicate with you.

We also may share customer and former customer information within our gotmortgage.com family and with valued partners (our employees) to evaluate eligibility, offer and recommend valuable products and services that may be right for you.

Customer Information Sharing Choices/Opt Out

Federal Law

Federal law requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect personal information about our customers. While Federal law allows us to share information about you to run our business, to perform services and offer our products, Federal law also gives you the right to limit some, but not all, sharing of your personal information.

Specifically, Federal law allows you to opt out/restrict us from sharing information as follows:

•           About your credit worthiness with our affiliates 

•           To non-affiliates to offer you their products and services 

State Laws

State laws may give you additional rights regarding our information sharing limitations.

We share personal information about you as permitted by the law of the state in which you reside and in accordance with federal law. As a customer of gotmortgage.com you received our Privacy Notice when you became our customer and you will receive our updated annual Privacy Notice each year you continue to be our customer.

You can limit us from sharing your information as permitted by law and as described in our Privacy Policy at any time by advising us of your Opt Out choices and how you do not want your information shared by calling 1-877-562-6976. You may notify us of your choices at any time.

If your past choices have not changed, you only need to tell us one time, as long as you have your account with us.

Customer Data Protection

We are a company committed to securing personal information and protecting the privacy of our customers. We use security measures that comply with federal law including assessing risk and using reasonable controls to protect customer information

Our company culture is to treat customer information the way we would want our own information treated. We train employees on handling and securing customer data to maintain a culture of protection and security. It is the responsibility of every associate, affiliate, and nonaffiliate to care for personal information about our customers.

Correcting Information

We are committed to maintaining accurate and up-to-date information on all of our customers. We may provide customers with access to account information in different ways, for example, over the telephone, online or on paper.

If you are a registered user of this website, you may be able to update some information online. You will need to log-into your account in order to utilize this feature.

How to contact us regarding your account:

U.S. Mail:

GotMortgage Customer Care

17220 Newhope St. Suite 213 

Fountain Valley, CA 92708 

Telephone: 1-877-562-6976

Email: info@gotmortgage.com 

Policy Effective Date

This Online Privacy Statement is effective May 25th, 2008 and remains in effect until amended. Gotmortgage.com reserves the right to amend this Privacy Statement or alter its privacy principles at its sole discretion without notice to you. We will post any alterations to this Privacy Statement on our web site in a timely manner so please check periodically.

Identity Theft / Fraudulent Activities

Identity Theft/Fraud

Identity Theft occurs when someone uses sensitive information, called Personally Identifiable Information (or PII) of another person without their permission to commit fraud or other crimes, such as Account Takeover or Application Fraud. [Account Takeover has occurred when an individual acquires another person's existing credit account information and purchases products and services at the victim's expense. Application Fraud has occurred when an individual uses another's Social Security Number or other Personally Identifiable Information to open new credit accounts in the victim's name.]

If you believe you are a victim of Identity Theft, contact the three major credit bureaus to place a fraud alert message on your credit file. When you place a fraud alert on your file, the credit reporting agencies will send you a copy of your credit report at no charge.

•           Experian (1-888-397-3742) 

•           Equifax (1-800-525-6285) 

•           TransUnion (1-800-680-7289) 

Carefully review your credit reports for: accounts you did not open, inquiries from creditors you did not initiate, and for personal information (such as home address and social security number) that is not accurate. If you see anything you do not understand or any accounts you did not open, call the credit reporting agency at the telephone number on the report.

If you decide not to place a fraud alert on your credit file, you can still obtain free copies of your credit report by going to the following Annual Credit Report website (www.annualcreditreport.com) or by calling them toll-free at 1-877-322-8228. (Hearing impaired consumers can access their TDD service at 1-877-730-4204.

To learn more about identity theft, visit the Federal Trade Commission's web site to receive further information and insights about how to protect your identity from identity thieves.

Identity Theft Hotline: 877-438-4338

Web: www.consumer.gov/idtheft

Mail: Identity Theft Clearinghouse,

Federal Trade Commission

600 Pennsylvania Ave., N.W., Washington, DC 20580
